Resha Puspita Dewi

Bandung, Jawa Barat | +6281 1234 7598 | reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/reshapuspita/ Github: github.com/renvelvet

Summary

Undergraduate Student in Information System and Technology major with internship experience as Web Developer. Enjoy content creation as an instrument to support my learning process. Confident to gain new experiences in a sector that can empower people to improve their level of needs continuously.

Skills

- Programming Languages: Ruby, Javascript, C++
- Database Management: MySQL, MongoDB
- Embedded Engineering: ESP32
- Testing Tools: Postman, Katalon Studios
- Basic Video Editing
- Basic Image Editing
- Well-organized

Experiences

Loker Programmer

Front End Programmer Intern (August 2020 - October 2020)

- Responsible to implement interactive website using ReactJS in collaborated with crossfunctional teams
- Integrated Front-End components with RESTful API to develop fully functioning web page

ProBotDev Sdn Bhd (Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia)

Scrum Master Apprenticeship (April 2019 - June 2019)

- Responsible to provide project boards for software engineer (SE) teams
- Responsible to enable scrum implementation in a team with 4 members
- Collaborate with product owner to deliver instruction to the team

Education

Institut Teknologi Bandung (2017-Present)

Information System and Technology

SMAN 24 Bandung (2013-2016)

Training/Certifications

- Electives Lite x Tokopedia Academy (June 2021)

 Testing in Scale with Tokopedia Engineering Productivity Course
- Telkom Digital Talent Incubator (DTI) (September 2020-December 2020)

 Backend Developer Talent
- Impact Byte (June 2020-August 2020)

 Full Stack Web Graduate

Volunteer and Organizations

HMIF ITB (March 2019-March 2021)

Academic and Welfare Staff

- Responsible to input study resources into shared drive throughout the semester
- Responsible to share information related to academics and scholarship with the members.

IAIF ITB Scholarship (October 2019)

Head of Logistic BNI ITB Ultra Marathon Event

• Lead logistic team to prepare basecamp used by alumni in the event.

Lingkar Sastra ITB (November 2017-May 2020)

Head of Infrastructure & Household Division (2019-2020)

Member of Craftmanship Division (2018-2019)

- Have a discussion with the member to appreciate literary works
- Responsible to organize seminars and competitions related to literature.
- Responsible to accommodate the literary works of members to be published into physical work.